Guide to the Radio Advertising Bureau Collection
University of Maryland Libraries
- Food, 1955-64; 194 items
  - Rice, Pasta & Sauces, 1958-63
    - Contadina Spaghetti Sauce, undated (Folder 2.0)
    - Contadina Tomato Paste, 1961 (Folder 3.0)
    - Franco-American, undated (Folder 4.0)
    - Golden Grain Pasta, 1963 (Folder 5.0)
    - Goodman's Noodles, 1960 (Folder 6.0)
    - Inn Maid Noodles, 1961 (Folder 7.0)
    - LaRosa, 1958, 1962 (Folder 8.0)
    - Lawry's Spaghetti Sauce, 1960 (Folder 9.0)
    - Mueller's, undated (Folder 10.0)
    - Ronzoni, 1960, 1962 (Folder 11.0)
  - Pet Food, 1958-61
    - Cadillac Dog Food, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 1.0)
    - Friskies Cat Food, 1959 (Folder 2.0)
    - Ken-L-Ration, 1958 (Folder 3.0)
    - Nutrena Dog Food, undated (Folder 4.0)
    - Sturdy Dog Food, 1961 (Folder 5.0)
  - Frozen Foods, 1958-65
    - Bird's Eye Meat Pies, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 1.0)
    - Crystal Ice, 1959 (Folder 2.0)
    - Dulany Frozen Foods, 1957-58 (Folder 3.0)
  - Processed Foods, 1956-64
    - Aunt Nellie's Foods, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 1.0)
    - Banquet Canning Company, 1960 (Folder 2.0)
    - Beech Nut Baby Foods, 1958 (Folder 3.0)
    - Bounty Chili, undated (Folder 4.0)
    - California Canners & Growers, 1965 (Folder 5.0)
    - Campbell Soup Co., 1960 (Folder 6.0)
    - Carnation Tuna, 1962 (Folder 7.0)
    - Chun King Chow Mein, 1960-61 (Folder 8.0)
    - Dennison's Chili Con Carne, 1961 (Folder 9.0)
    - Fluffy Instant Potatoes, 1958 (Folder 10.0)
    - Heinz Beans, 1961 (Folder 11.0)
    - Heinz Cheese Soup, 1961 (Folder 12.0)
    - La Choy Chinese Foods, 1963 (Folder 13.0)
    - LaRosa Soups, 1958 (Folder 14.0)
    - Manischewitz Borscht, 1959 (Folder 15.0)
    - Rosarita Mexican Foods, 1962 (Folder 16.0)
    - Vita Food Products, 1964-65 (Folder 17.0)
  - Condiments, 1957-63
    - Fanning's Bread and Butter Pickles, undated (Box 46, Folder 1.0)
    - Gem Salad Oil, 1964 (Folder 2.0)
    - Grey Poupon, 1956 (Folder 3.0)
    - Heinz Pickles, 1964 (Folder 4.0)
    - Hellman's-Heinz, 1961 (Folder 5.0)
    - Mary Ellen's Jams & Jellies, undated (Folder 6.0)
    - Mazola Dressings, 1963 (Folder 7.0)
    - Ocean Spray, undated (Folder 8.0)
    - Polaner Preserves, undated (Folder 9.0)
  - Spices, 1960-65
    - Ac'cent, 1962-63 (Box 47, Folder 1.0)
    - Angosturra Aromatic Bitters, 1961 (Folder 2.0)
    - Diamond Crystal Salt, undated (Folder 3.0)
    - Sterling Salt, 1957-58 (Folder 4.0)
  - Baking, 1958-64
    - Albers Cereals, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 1.0)
    - Ballard Flour, 1960 (Folder 2.0)
    - Bisquick, 1965 (Folder 3.0)
    - C&H Sugar, 1962-63 (Folder 4.0)
    - Light Crust Flour, 1961 (Folder 5.0)
    - Mazola, 1963 (Folder 6.0)
    - Pillsbury Best Flour, 1960 (Folder 7.0)
- Household Products, 1959-63; 2 items
  - Alcoa Wrap, 1959, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 1.0)